KAIJYU THEATER PRESENTS
REGULAR SIZE MONSTERS SERIES
SHINYA TSUKAMOTO 'S FILM
TOMOROWO TAGUCHI IN
TETSUO
- Hello ? - Hello .
Are you alright ?
You know , I 've felt very strange
ever since the hit-and-run accident .
Come on , then .
- Come on , then ! - Stop !
Stop !
Ah , it hurts !
What 's the matter ?
Hey , what 's the matter ?
It 's nothing .
Nothing .
Don 't ever ...
leave me , okay ?
What is it ?
Stop . Don 't open the door ! This is too much to take .
Don 't open it !
Just show me .
Nothing much scares me .
No way . Stay away !
What 's going on ?
How did this happen to me ?
Listen , just open up .
No way !
I told you ... I don 't scare easily !
Okay , you like what you see ?
I can 't show you any more .
I 'm being punished . That must be it .
I told you I could take it .
Don 't leave me alone !
Nothing shocks me .
Fuck it ! Fuck it !
You can take it , huh ?
Stop !
You want a taste of my sewage pipe ?
What the fuck is this ? This is unbelievable .
How did you make it here ?
There 's a piece of metal stuck in your brain .
I can 't believe you 're still alive .
What genius inserted it ?
You 'll die instantly if it 's removed .
Oh , well ... just think of it as a piece of jewellery .
It 's repaired .
So you 've done it again . Don 't hang up .
I know all about you .
You can 't escape me .
Drop dead , you metal freak !
Are you alright ? Are you okay ?
Are you alright ?
Hey , he 's watching us . He 's looking at us !
Honey ... he 's watching us . He 's watching us !
- Fantastic . - You didn 't die .
Long time no see .
Soon even your brain will turn into metal .
Let me show you something wonderful . A new world ...
Come on , then !
Hey , come on !
Come on !
Sonny .
Stop it !
Stop ! Stop !
Stop !
Come on !
You see all this rust on my body ?
My first metal implant was already rusty ,
before my cells began to assimilate it .
But your shaver was stainless steel .
I 'll finish you .
Fuck you ! Don 't you understand ?
Your future is metal !
Damn , you want to rust yourself to death ?
Stop resisting !
Ah ... I feel great .
We can mutate the whole world into metal .
We can rust the world into the dust of the universe .
Sounds interesting .
Our love can destroy this whole fucking world !
Get them !
SALARYMAN : TOMOROWO TAGUCHI GIRLFRIEND : KEI FUJIWARA
WOMAN IN GLASSES : NOBU KANAOKA FETISHIST : SHINYA TSUKAMOTO
DOCTOR : NAOMASA MUSAKA TRAMP : RENJI ISHIBASHI
SCRIPT , ART DIRECTION , LIGHTING , EDITING , SFX BY SHINYA TSUKAMOTO
COSTUMES BY KEI FUJIWARA
CINEMATOGRAPHY BY SHINYA TSUKAMOTO KEI FUJIWARA
MUSIC BY CHU ISHIKAWA
DIRECTED BY SHINYA TSUKAMOTO